imotiv.ly 2014-06-29

# Imotiv | Privacy Policy

**Dated: 17 September 2012**

Imotiv Pte Ltd (hereinafter referred as “We” or “Us” or “Our”) digests blog posts from around the world and simplifies them for you to read with our patent-pending technology. Such service is provided through various electronic platforms such as mobile application and website (“Application”) 

## COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

When you register an account with us, we will collect your name, email addresses or certain personally identifiable information. When you access or use the Application, we will collect information such as:- 

  1. your activities through the Application,
  2. any information that you may send to us and any information you may post to the Application, and
  3. information collected through the use of Cookies or Device Identifiers (as defined below).

We also collect personal information when you:-

  1. follow a website, provide comments or submit a problem to us,
  2. request information from us and provide your name or return contact information, or
  3. respond to special offers, contests or surveys.

The personal information as collected (unless stated otherwise) is obligatory on you and if you fail to provide any information as required, it may affect your application for an account with us and/or the performance of the Application. 

Some of the information collected by us may not be explicitly submitted by you as we also automatically receives and records information on its server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookie information, the web pages you request, your browser type and language, access times, and the referring web site address. 

If you give us information about another person, you confirm that the other person has appointed you to act on his/her behalf and has agreed that you can: 

  1. give consent on his/her behalf to the processing of his or her personal information;
  2. receive in his/her behalf any data protection notices; and
  3. warrant that you have obtained his/her consent for us to store his/her personal information.

## COOKIES

"Cookies" are data files that may be downloaded to your computer when you access or use the Application and permit the Application to identify your browser whenever you interact with the Application. We may use cookies to recognize repeat visits by users of the Application and to collect information about our users’ interactions with the Application. These cookies contain identification information that enables us to streamline your experiences using the Application. You may set your browser software to reject cookies, but you may not be able to optimize the features of the Application. In some cases, you may not be able to access the Application if cookies are disabled. 

## DEVICE IDENTIFIERS

When you use a mobile device like a tablet or phone to access the Application, we may access, collect, monitor, store on your device, and/or remotely store one or more "device identifiers." Device identifiers are small data files or similar data structures stored on or associated with your mobile device, which uniquely identify your mobile device. A device identifier may be data stored in connection with the device hardware, data stored in connection with the device's operating system or other software, or data sent to the device by the Application. 

A device identifier may deliver information to us or to a third party partner about how you browse and use the Application and may help us or others provide reports or personalized content and ads. Some features of the Application may not function properly if use or availability of device identifiers is impaired or disabled. 

## EXTERNAL LINKS

As a part of the Application, we provide links to web sites operated by third parties. We are not responsible for the information collection or privacy practices or the content of those third party sites. 

## EXTERNAL SURVEYS

We may collect information through reader surveys published on Application under our network. We retain the right to analyze, process, use and share this information with advertisers in order to segment the users n the hope of feeding relevant ads to users. 

## USE OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION

In general, we may use the information provided to us for the following purposes:- 

  1. provide, maintain, protect and improve the Application, to develop new applications, and to protect ourselves and our users;
  2. manage your account and provide you with customer support;
  3. develop and display content tailored to your interests on the Application;
  4. verify your eligibility and deliver prizes in connection with any contests and giveaways that the Application may have;
  5. enforce any terms and conditions between us;
  6. research purposes including historical and statistical purposes;
  7. general operation and maintenance of the Application including audit and its related portal(s); 
  8. provide you with regular communications (other than direct marketing materials) from us relating to the Application; and
  9. investigation of complaints, suspected suspicious transactions and research for service improvement.

Some of your information such as your name and picture will be made public in a form of a public profile. 

We may also use your personal details and website preferences in presentations, marketing materials, user lists, financial reports and web site listings. 

## DISCLOSURE OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION

We may share you information with other companies in the Netccentric Group of Companies which Imotiv is a part of. 

We may share aggregated and non-personally identifiable information about you with third parties such as advertisers. Such information does not identify you individually. 

We may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or if we have good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary to protect and/or defend our rights and interests. We may, as permitted by applicable law, disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties in connection with an investigation of fraud, infringement, piracy, tax avoidance and evasion or other unlawful activity and you expressly authorize us to make such disclosures. 

All personally identifying information collected by us are stored in our servers. Such servers may be located outside your country and you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. 

If we are merged or acquired by another entity, personally identifiable information may be transferred to such entity as a part of the merger or acquisition. 

## REVIEW AND MODIFICATIONS TO YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION.

You may add, modify or update your email address, name, and other information by accessing your profile page. It is your responsibility to ensure that the information you have on the Application is the most up-to-date information as possible. We may retain transactional history in order to document a transaction you may have had with us. 

However, we reserve the right to decline to process requests which jeopardize the security and privacy of the personal information of others as well as requests which are impractical or not made in good faith. 

Where you elect to limit our right to process the personal data, you may contact us in writing. For avoidance of doubt, the limitation does not include processing of mandatory personal data namely your name and email. 

## SECURITY

We store all information including personally identifiable information obtained through registration securely and considers it part of the assets of its business. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information it collects online. However, data security is a constantly evolving art and science. You should consider any communication that you transmit to us (such as data, questions or answers, comments, or suggestions) as non-confidential, and agree that we will not be liable or responsible if information that belongs to you is intercepted and used by an unintended recipient. 

## CHANGE TO THIS POLICY

If this privacy policy changes in any way, it will be updated on this page. Regularly reviewing this page ensures you are updated on the information which is collected, how it is used and under what circumstances, if any, it is shared with other parties.
